Lola Hopper collection, Inclusive: 1965-2013, undated, Bulk: 1971-1977, 2008, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Personal, 1965-1990, undated; 5
  - Denim jacket with campaign button sleeves, Embroidered State of Texas on front, Embroidered American flag on back, Democratic Party pocket square, undated (Box 18 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Two flags, Texas flag and USA flag, undated (Box 18 OVZ, Folder 2)